https://www.linkedin.com/in/bellarball/

(737) 228-0031 · mohawkball@gmail.com

CAREER PROFILE

Management Information Systems and Data Science candidate experienced in Python, data analysis, and analyzing statistics. Analytical thinker excelling at data modeling, project management, and cross-team communication. Highly motivated worker with an aptitude to learn, passion for innovation, and motivated to work independently, and willing to learn other scripting languages.

EDUCATION

BAYLOR UNIVERSITY –Waco, Texas

December 2024

Bachelor of Business Administration

- Management Information Systems; GPA 3.6
- Data Science Minor
- Hankamer Scholars; Honors College

EXPERIENCE

Baylor W.R. Poage Legislative Library

January 2022 - Present

Archival Assistant and Desk Attendant

- Posted on social media once monthly following library's vision
- Prepared files for archives by removing confidential and/or irrelevant information
- Protected files from 1940 1975 by removing harmful materials and storing properly

Code2College

June 2023 - August 2023

Software Development Lead Intern - Data & Analytics Team

- Collaborated with senior curriculum management to define strategic learning objectives
- Enhanced and expedited curriculum development by coding and documenting course projects
- Authored course materials on data analysis topics, catering to beginners and advanced learners

Good Faith Media

June 2023 - August 2023

Summer Intern

- · Digitally sorted hundreds of videos to be easier for viewers to find
- Wrote opinion and news pieces on relevant topics representing the view of the company

ADDITIONAL

- **Computer Skills:** Python, SQL, C++, R, Tableau, Excel Macro Scripting, Statistical Modeling Software, Data Visualization, Project Documentation, Quantitative Analysis
- Foreign Languages: Basic German Basic written and verbal communication skills
- Organizations: Table Talk Graphic Designer, Ballroom Dance Club Treasurer, Data Science Club, Student Dining Advisory Committee
- Activities: Code2College HackTogether, Honors Book Club, Baylor Ethics Case, Association for Information Systems